87, New York City Medicine,
coolly-hack of the kleinen unplugged I
look up to the stars and reach for the sky.
I believe in tomorrow if we try.
I back on it.
Come on let's go everybody!
Oh we share the music.
We share the music.
Come on let's go baby baby.
Oh we share the one dream.
Come on let's go everybody.
Oh we share the good times.
We share the good times.
Let's go, baby, baby, oh,
we share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see, but to believe.
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we.
Feel the rush brought on by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat.
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try high.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
Oh, as we chase, we're being chased.
From the top we go, one straight and wild.
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good.
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I.
Share the one dream, I know where you are.
Share the good times, show us that smile.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go, beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow if we try.
I know that you are there,
just on the other side.
Wait there for me, soon
it will be you and I.
Then let us go, beyond, far and wide.
I believe in the one world if we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
That's it for me.
I've got muscle cramps.
Well, I know that I have many
muscles to cramp in the first place.
Hey, nice work back there, Brooke.
You really thinned those
fish riders out, huh?
Uh-huh.
Happy to be of service.
And I think I need a moment of respite.
Zoro, it's just as I thought.
Your injuries from Thriller
Bark haven't healed.
Injured or not, there's no way
I'm losing to a bunch of fish.
I'll be fine.
You!
Don't let your guard down, Roronoa!
Six-sword style!
Tentacle sword! Overload!
Was that you paying me back for last time?
Nah, not really, but you
two gotta watch your backs.
That was super cool, Hatchan!
Yeah, I told him you were strong!
You really?
Die, fish man!
Oops! Pardon me!
You?
I thought I was gonna die!
Thanks a lot, you guys!
Oh, it was my pleasure.
Who needs to watch us back again?
We can't take him alone!
Revert to formation!
Huh? Pervert?
You called?
Convert!
Fly high formation!
Pervert fly guy?
That's gotta be me!
They're not talking about you!
Get ready!
Over here! Hey!
Come get me!
She's cute.
Well, that's a damn shame.
The head's said to kill them all!
I'd like to see you try.
What the hell? Whoa!
Too bad. Mirage tempo.
Oh, and watch out for those
thunder clouds, by the way!
Dos manos.
Clutch.
Cloven!
Diamond!
Convert again! Quick!
Yeah? What do you want?
Shut up!
Eat this! You sure?
Maybe I need to get my ears checked.
Whoa! Oh, crap!
That pervert is bulletproof!
Strong hammer!
They're tough!
Like, super-duper tough!
Did you see? Oh, yeah.
These guys are tough, all right.
But I thought we'd just grab
Hachi and maybe get out of here,
not fight to the last man.
A little bit closer!
Hey, Franky, we gotta
pull the ship ashore.
They've got the upper hand in the ocean!
Out here, we're nothing but sitting ducks?
Yeah, but you think they don't know that?
This is their base.
If we try to move the ship, they'll
just come at us twice as hard!
Luffy!
Big one coming through!
Iron mask guy?
Yeah, and he's on a huge cow! Cow?
And you!
That sounds like more to
follow! It's the head!
Look at you, getting swatted
down left and right. Oh, crap!
What the heck is that?
You're not mosquitoes, men.
You're flying fish riders.
Did he just crush his own house?
With the Straw Hats dead,
I won't need this base!
Don't hold back!
Hen, we're sorry.
We'll drag him off to the
sea and finish him for sure.
Move it!
I don't care about fishmen or
mermaids or giant talking gloves.
I'll give you five seconds to
get the hell out of my way.
Okay, but I'm a starfish.
Huh.
I didn't get into the slave
trade market because I wanted to.
You know that, don't you?
Of course, Hen.
Good luck!
This is the greatest day of my life.
The man that I've dreamed of
killing is right before my eyes.
I may have suffered to get here,
but it's all been worth it.
I gotta admit that miracles
can happen after all.
I never did a damn thing to that
bastard and he made my life hell!
He ruined me!
Hey, what's his deal?
Is he talking to us?
I've got nothing to lose anymore.
I'm ending this.
Even if I die, I'm killing you.
Do you hear me?
Black-leg Sanji!
I've been waiting for this for a
long time. He's mad! His accent!
It's starting to come out!
Me?
What in the hell did I
do? That's weird. Sanji!
Hey, what gives?
What the heck did you do to
piss this guy off so bad?
Maybe something back on the Baratier?
Come on, try to remember!
Well, if we're going back that far...
Uh, I did all sorts of
stuff to piss people off.
Jeez, I can't even count them all.
Well, better let them kill you then.
Don't play dumb with me, blackleg.
It wasn't that long ago, damn it!
Look out!
Those are harpoons!
Huh, if it was something
recent, I'm even more confused.
Whoa, this is not good, guys.
There's something up with these harpoons!
My scorpion harpoons
are packed with poison.
If they so much as nick you,
you won't last three minutes.
I'm gonna kill you and your friends.
Watch out!
Dammit, who in the hell is this bastard?
Just tell me!
You reef what you sow, Blackleg!
I saw what was under that
mask of his. Oh, yeah?
Then who is he?
You'll be surprised, but
you've seen his face. I have.
Ah! That bug!
He knocked out Master Duvall's mask!
Go ahead. Look.
See this cursed face of mine.
You're kidding.
I can cry.
I've been waiting for this day.
I knew I couldn't let you live.
So I set out to see to put an end to this.
But I knew I had my work cut out for me.
Because your wanted poster
didn't look nothing like you.
Even if the Navy or some
bounty hunter saw you,
they'd never know they were
looking at the guy on the poster.
But they found someone else.
Someone they hounded day
in and day out. Oh, head.
And when they found him, do
you know what they'd say?
You can't hide from us
Black-Legged Sanji
And then, do you know what I told him?
I've never even met the guy before
And not only that, I ain't even a pirate
Black-Legged Sanji You ruined
me This is all your fault
Hey Sanji, where are you going?
Can you imagine how
scared I was being hunted
like an animal the navy
headquarters hounded me?
At every turn famous bounty hunters
knocking at my door I didn't want to
hurt nobody I just Wanted a life of
peace and quiet and you destroyed it!
Hey?
What did I ever do to you?
Give me back My life!
Black leg! Sanji!
Who cares?
Ahead!
Listen up you punk!
If you don't take responsibility
for this Then who will huh?
Shut the hell up!
I'm more pissed off about the
stupid wanted poster than anyone!
In a way I guess they both got it back!
I wasn't expecting that!
What a crazy world we live in?
I don't know if it's a
lucky one or an unlucky one!
But he must have been born
under some kind of star!
Whether this is a miracle or a
tragedy It's entertaining either way!
Hey guys?
Do you think we can
make friends with Devil?
They really do look the same, don't they?
Two peas in a pod.
When are I done with this guy?
I'm gonna flatten you!
You go ahead and take care of things.
We'll sit this one out.
Don't act like it's my fault!
If you didn't want to look
like the stupid wanted poster,
then why didn't you
just cut your damn hair
or grow a beard instead
of trying to kill me?
Ha!
I didn't think of that!
If you're that stupid, you
can only blame yourself!
Just shut up and listen to me!
We just wanted a simple
life, nothing fancy.
We weren't so bad.
We were running a humble little
criminal outfit in these parts.
Just trying to make ends meet
We didn't do anything wrong we just
extorted some money from people.
It was a simple life, but a happy one
I don't know what you're
doing all the way out here,
but we found you now surrender and save
us all some trouble I ain't telling you!
I ain't even met the guy!
Understand, Blackleg, it's not my fault.
I never wanted to cause any trouble.
And suddenly I get a bounty of 77 million
because you don't know how to behave.
A small-town guy like me can't stand
up to all those powerful marines.
They hunted me down.
And now I gotta hide behind that iron
mask so nobody will recognize my face.
My whole life is ruined because
you decided to be a damn pirate.
I'm gonna chase you all the way to the
end of hell if that's what it takes.
And if you got a problem with that,
then why don't you just kill
me and get it over with?
Help me.
He's killing me.
You're telling me you put Nami and
Robin in danger even though they have
nothing to do with this because some
moron drew a crappy picture of me?
Because they're part of the crew that made
you a famous pirate in the first place.
If I'm gonna take revenge,
I might as well wipe out the rest
of your crew while I'm at it, right?
None of you are making it out alive!
Poison harpoons!
Convert to trap mode.
Huh?
Pervert?
This looks bad.
Sanji!
They're going to pull him
into the ocean and drown him!
Sanji, get out of there quick!
It's no use.
It's made of iron.
Say hello to a watery grave.
Oh, no!
Hang in there, Sanji!
I'll save you!
We don't need both of you drowning.
Let me handle this one. I'm on it!
You humans are too slow underwater.
You'll never catch up in time.
You're right, but you don't stand a
chance against the speed of my men.
Come on, even you should know that flying
fish are the fastest creatures in the sea.
And my men have oxygen tanks,
so they can take their
sweet time making sure your
little friend is nice and
dead by the time he comes up.
See?
I thought of everything.
You!
I wish I could have crushed the life out
of that bastard with my own two hands,
but at least I know he'll die suffering.
What did you say?
This is what happens when
you piss off the head, pal.
I'm gonna pass out.
Katie, no!
Hey, cowboy.
I think you may have forgotten
about a little somewhat.
Like you said, flying fish are
definitely faster than fishmen.
And when it comes to sea creatures,
they're in the top class.
But, just to let you know, there is one
creature that's even faster than that.
Mermaids.
In every sea in this wide world,
there's nothing great or small
that can out-swim a mermaid.
Don't worry, Sanjichin.
I'll be there real soon, okay? Hold on!
She's really that awesome?
I never knew Yeah,
and if she wasn't spacing out all the time,
nothing would ever be able to catch her?
It is what it is.
I see.
Kuma!
We're counting on you! Good luck!
Uh-oh, what is that?
Looks like an anchor,
but crap, that's huge!
Aim for the center of the ship.
Once we drop this,
they'll sink like a rock.
Some of them have Devil Fruit power,
so that'll take out half the crew.
There's no way we can
survive that. Dodge it!
Use the burst for the battle!
It's your time!
No, it's too late!
Usopp, hurry! Come with me!
Okay.
Go to the bow and stay on standby!
I don't get it, but whatever you say!
We're gonna bust out
our super secret weapon!
What super secret weapon?
I'm gonna stick to Sonny!
Somebody do something!
Anything!
Sonny won't die. Believe it.
The main is spinning!
Is that supposed to happen? Now die!
Franky, hurry!
Emergency evacuation secret
weapon, Chicken Voyage!
Oh, they dodged it!
Hey, that's cheating!
How the hell do you make your ship
go backwards in the first place?
Usopp, get inside the prowl! Get inside?
Whoa, it opens!
Don't worry, brother.
We're not just running away.
The Sunny's got another trick that's
about to knock your socks off.
Usopp!
Cola energy charging!
What is that? Uh-oh.
Charging complete.
Hey, what am I supposed to do now?
Get as many as you can
in the circle. A circle?
Like this?
Okay, they're in.
Lock on with the button below you,
then pull the lever. Blow me, huh? Ha.
Hey, look, it's glowing!
Down, cannon!
Fire!
Amazing!
You're way too impressed with this.
Ha!
How you like that?
Now you've seen the Sonny's true power.
You've got almost all the
flying fish guys in one shot!
Well, you can thank Usopp for that one.
Not bad for a first try, huh?
Whoa!
Yes, Scooby! Sonny!
Good show, Mr. Lion!
My eyes nearly popped out of my head!
Or, hey, what up, if I had any.
Chicken Voyage uses three
barrels of cola up front.
But right after,
it also fires a two-barrel
coup to burst in
back to stop the ship
from getting blown away.
In other words, it uses a buttload of cola,
so it's not something we can do often.
She tanned us up in the net!
Damn it, that mermaid's fast!
Hold on, Sanji-Chen, we're gonna make it!
We're almost there!
Kuma!
Oh, thank goodness!
Is Sanji okay?
I don't know, but something's wrong.
He's losing a bunch of
blood for some reason.
Huh?
Is he dying?
I thought he was okay at first, but
blood started pouring out of his nose.
Uh, nosebleed.
Nah, he's fine.
If he wants to die like
that, then let him.
Yep, it's what he would have wanted.
Hang in there, Sanjie Chen!
Did I die and go to heaven?
You little punk, if you weren't
friends with a mermaid, you'd be dead.
Looks like you lost a
lot of men back there?
Shut your mouth!
I don't need the flying fish riders
as long as I've got Motobalo.
You think I ride this guy
because he looks cool? Ha!
Countless have fallen prey to his horns He
poked holes in the village dam back home.
And if you try putting him in
a cage, he smashes the bars!
The marines keep hounding me.
But I escape them every time because this
guy's always ready to bust some heads.
They don't call his horns the
heart rippers for nothing.
Okay, let's rock!
Go, Motobolo!
Luffy, no!
The horse can't even reach him!
There's no point in fighting, you big cow.
Stop it!
Motobolo, what's wrong?
Cal's acting weird all of a sudden
what
happened
guess it passed
out did I just miss something hey
Luffy what was that I didn't do
anything I think oh what is my life
sucks so much whatever he did it
didn't seem like an attack it's more
More like he won the animal over,
or at least knocked it over when
he spoke to it face to face.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you saying he psyched the thing out?
Sure, Luffy's tough, but
that ox doesn't know that.
Maybe it's just a Secret cow.
Straw Hat, I'm gonna murder you!
Hey, hold on, Luffy.
Sanji!
Glad you made it out okay.
Stand back and let me
take care of this whiner.
I just met him, and he's already
been a pain in my ass for too long.
Your ass?
Look who's talking, black
leg, until you're dead.
An innocent guy like me can't find
a moment of peace in this world.
You're the criminal here, and I'm
sick of paying for your crimes.
That's enough.
How do you think I feel seeing
that crappy picture come to life?
A stupid face like that
shouldn't exist in this world.
You don't want to see it?
Then just die!
Yeah! Dance!
Show it!
Push it! Dance! Let's go!
Please stop it!
Arasha!
Now eat this.
That's a full course of my best
techniques served up free of charge,
and it's the last you'll ever
taste, you piece of crap.